<add>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.coursera.org/course/1styearteachingms-hs</field>
	<field name="course_title">First Year Teaching (Secondary Grades) - Success from the Start | Coursera</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_workload">2-4hours of work / week</field>
	<field name="course_language">English</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Ellen Moir</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Lynn Kepp</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">New Teacher Center</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">New Teacher Center</field>
	<field name="course_category">Education</field>
	<field name="course_category">Teacher Professional Development</field>
	<field name="course_intro">First Year Teaching (Secondary Grades) - Success from the Start
Success with your students starts on Day 1. Learn from NTC&#39;s 25 years developing key skills and strategies to create positive, productive classroom environments where students thrive. Build relationships with Secondary Grade (6-12) students, establish and maintain behavioral expectations, implement classroom procedures and routines, and use instructional time effectively.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About the Course
Developing mastery in establishing and maintaining a rich learning environment is one of the great joys of being a teacher. This course will provide high leverage strategies, resources, and support for professional growth so that you can provide students with the engaging, safe environment essential for student learning. This course is aligned to the needs of Secondary Grade teachers (6-12 grade, usually teaching multiple sections of the same content area, like math, fine arts, science, etc. to students 12 years and older).

This course will teach you how to implement research-based strategies in the following areas: 
Setting and communicating high expectations for students;
Building positive relationships with and between students;
Organizing the learning environment;
Behavioral preventions and interventions; and
Establishing and maintaining routines and procedures that support student learning.
Stellar classrooms don’t just happen—they’re created with the kind of intentional planning and preparation this course offers so that you and your students can be successful from the start!

Recommended Background
Actively teaching, preparing to teach, or interested in teaching in the Secondary Grades (departmental 6-12).

Course Format
The class will consist of videos and discussion posts.  Participants will be expected to respond to instructor and peer discussion posts. Assignments will be classroom based and will be assessed by peers according to provided rubrics.  An end-of-course reflection and survey are required for completion.

FAQ
Will I get a Statement of Accomplishment after completing this class?
Yes. Students who successfully complete the class will receive a Statement of Accomplishment signed by the instructor.

What resources will I need for this class?
For this course, all you need is an Internet connection, and the time to read, write, discuss, and learn about becoming a successful beginning teacher.

I am not sure if I should enroll here, or should enroll in the other course aligned with Elementary Grades. Which course will work best for me?
If you teach in a department based classroom, usually teaching multiple sections in Middle or High School, where you specialize by teaching math, foreign language, language arts, etc. to students usually older than 12, then this is your course! But if you are interested in teaching all subjects in a self-contained classroom, usually in Elementary School (K-5 or K-6) then you should enroll in First Year Teaching (Elementary Grades) - Success from the Start.</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.coursera.org/course/4dimensions</field>
	<field name="course_title">Climate Change in Four Dimensions | Coursera</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">10 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">5-7hours of work / week</field>
	<field name="course_language">English</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Charles Kennel</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Naomi Oreskes</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Veerabhadran Ramanathan</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Richard Somerville</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">David G. Victor</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Charles Kennel</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Naomi Oreskes</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Veerabhadran Ramanathan</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Richard Somerville</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">David G. Victor</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of California, San Diego</field>
	<field name="course_category">Economics &amp; Finance</field>
	<field name="course_category">Health &amp; Society</field>
	<field name="course_category">Physical &amp; Earth Sciences</field>
	<field name="course_category">Biology &amp; Life Sciences</field>
	<field name="course_category">Social Sciences</field>
	<field name="course_category">Law</field>
	<field name="course_category">Energy &amp; Earth Sciences</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Climate Change in Four Dimensions
This course views climate change from a variety of perspectives at the intersection of the natural sciences, technology, and the social sciences and humanities.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About the Course
This course views climate change from a variety of perspectives at the intersection of the natural sciences, technology, and the social sciences and humanities. 
 
Specific topics included are:

the scientific basis for human-induced climate change, including uncertainties and controversies, the historical context for identifying the climate problem, links to other issues such as air pollution, and the evidence for extreme as well as irreversible climate changes;
communication and social responses to the scientific evidence, including the role of science in the media;
assessment of climate impacts and adaptive management; and
mitigation of emissions, including the design of national policy instruments, the roles of market failures such as in technological innovation, and the role of institutions in managing international collective action. 
Course Syllabus
Below you will find the course topics for each week. You will have access to a more detailed syllabus on the course start date.

This course has 19 lessons, weekly activities, a mid-term, and a final exam. The topics are as follows: 
Week 1: Basic Science of Climate Change

Lesson 1: Climate Change Science: History, Foundations, Detection, Attribution
Lesson 2: How Much Will Climate Change? Climate Models and Sensitivity
Week 2: The Nature of Scientific Knowledge

Lesson 3: The Scientific Consensus on Climate Change: 
How Do We Know We’re Not Wrong? Part 1
Lesson 4: The Scientific Consensus on Climate Change: 
How Do We Know We’re Not Wrong? Part 2
Week 3: Climate Change Mitigation

Lesson 5: Physics and chemistry of climate mitigation
Lesson 6: Why Climate is an International Problem
Week 4: International dimensions of climate change

Lesson 7: International Cooperation on the Ozone Layer: 
A Useful Model?
Lesson 8: International Cooperation on Climate Change: 
Models for Reform (with a Focus on Mitigation)
Week 5: The Impacts of Climate Change

Lesson 9: Extreme weather, climate change and communication 
Lesson 10: Impacts of Climate Change
Week 6: What may be in store for the world?

Mid-term
Lesson 11: Coping with Climate Change in the Next Half-Century  
Week 7: How the public views climate change

Lesson 12: Merchants of Doubt, Part 1
Lesson 13: Merchants of Doubt, Part 2
Week 8: How regions are preparing to adapt

Lesson 14: Ice, Snow, and Water
Lesson 15: Arctic and California Climate Change Assessments
Week 9: What we can do, Part 1

Lesson 16: What if climate change turns ugly? The Pros and Cons of Geoengineering.
Lesson 17: Technology Innovation (With a Focus on Energy)
Week 10: What we can do, Part 2

Lesson 18: It’s Not Too Late to Mitigate
Lesson 19: Avoid the Unmanageable, Manage the Unavoidable
Recommended Background
The course is designed for individuals with previous collegiate experience, and will be taught in an online lecture format. There are no specific background requirements and everyone is welcome. It will be helpful to you if you have experience in interpreting data as well as graphic representations of data and to have a familiarity with basic principles of natural and physical science.

Suggested Readings
Required and optional readings are aligned with the weekly lesson learning objectives. There is no required textbook.  Open Educational Resources are being used in this course.  For example, during week one this is a required reading and is made available to students as a PDF document:
IPCC, 2007: Summary for Policymakers. IPCC, 2007: Summary for Policymakers. In: Climate Change 2007: The Physical Science Basis. Contribution of Working Group I to the Fourth Assessment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change [Solomon, S., D. Qin, M. Manning, Z. Chen, M. Marquis, K.B. Averyt, M.Tignor and H.L. Miller (eds.)]. Cambridge University Press, Cambridge, United Kingdom and New York, NY, USA. 

Course Format
19 video lectures given by professors Charles Kennel, Naomi Oreskes, Richard Somerville, and David Victor are the foundation of this ten week course. 
There is an additional presentation by  Veerabhadran Ramanathan.
Students may review released video lectures at any time during the course. 
Interactive simulations, web links, and videos explain and enrich lesson topics.
Students will collaborate with students from around the world on learning activities. For example, during week one students will predict and calculate their carbon footprint; consider ways they could reduce their footprint; collaborate with students from other regions to compare their findings using social media; and, finally, reflect  on what they learned and write a paragraph or two about their experience.
A weekly live interactive session will summarize the previous week’s content, bridge to the upcoming week’s learning objectives, and allow students to ask questions.
The “Ask The Professor” section answers frequently asked scientific, policy, international, and social questions pertaining to climate change.
The Discussion Forum fosters relevant and enriching interaction between participants. 
 “Check Your Knowledge” questions help students reinforce the lesson’s material.
Weekly quiz questions are based on defined lesson learning objectives.
Use of notes, access to lecture materials, and three attempts per quiz  is permissible. 
Course grades are based on quizzes, activities, the mid-term, and the final exam.
Professional credit from UC San Diego is available by enrolling in, and successfully completing, a companion course at UC San Diego Extension.  The companion course does have a fee, and builds upon the information presented in this course, with increased interactivity, assignments, and demonstration of mastery.  For more information about earning credit for this course, please visit: UC San Diego Extension. 
FAQ
Frequently Asked Questions 
If you can’t find an answer to your question, please send us an email with your question: unex-mooc@ucsd.edu

Who is providing this course? 
The Scripps Institution of Oceanography, a department of the University of California San Diego provides the content for this massive open online course (or MOOC) in partnership with UC San Diego Extension. 

What is this course like? 
This course consists of 19 lessons. Each lesson features short video lectures by professors Charles Kennel, Naomi Oreskes, Richard Somerville, Veerabhadran Ramanathan, and David Victor. Included with each lesson are quizzes and additional resources in the form of interactive simulations, web links, and videos. Most weeks for 10 weeks, two lessons will be released. You can watch the video lectures at any time during the course.  At the end of each week, there is a quiz to help you determine if you understand that week’s lessons. At the end of the course there is a final exam. Your scores from the quizzes, activities, mid-term and final exam  will establish your content mastery level. 
How much does it cost? 
The course is available for free. If you would like to receive credit for participation in the course, you can obtain credit through UC San Diego Extension. See the &quot;How Do I Get Credit?&quot; section in this FAQ for more information. The content of the course is the same for both options. The difference between for-credit and no-credit classes are the level of interaction, nature of assignments, student support service, and demonstration of mastery that are part of the credit pathway. 

How can I provide feedback to the course management? 
You can provide feedback by emailing us at unex-mooc@ucsd.edu 
What language is the course available in? 
The course is presented and closed-captioned in English. Click the &quot;cc&quot; button on the video to view captions. English proficiency as represented by a TOEFL score of 550 or better is highly recommended for an optimal learning experience.   

How can I get the most out of the course? 
To get the most out of any course, it&#39;s important to be an active learner. Access the lessons as often as possible. Be sure to do the Check your knowledge exercises! It&#39;s also great to practice to engage with other students through the discussion forums,  meet-ups. or social media channels aligned with the course. Applying what you learn through different projects will also be vital to your learning. 

When does the course begin? 
The official start date for the course is: April 8th, 2014. This course is open for enrollment in advance even though the course is not yet available. You will be updated about the start dates after you register for the course. 

Are there deadlines within the course? 
Yes, there are due dates in this course. The course is structured to be taken over ten weeks. New lessons are released every week and are designed to be taken in the order they are provided. There are weekly readings, quizzes, and activities, a mid-term exam and a final exam - all with due dates. 
How long is the course available? 
The course will be available on the published start date, April 8th, 2014 and will run for ten weeks. Thereafter, the course materials will be available for your review for one month.

Are there course textbooks? 
There are no required textbooks for this course. All required and optional readings are made available to students through web links, PDF, or Word files. 
Is there a final exam? 
Yes, there is a final exam at the end of the course in the tenth week. 
Are there assignments? 
Yes, to learn any subject, it is important to check your knowledge and understanding of the concepts. Each lesson includes opportunities for you to evaluate your learning in both an ungraded and graded activity.  You will receive instant feedback on questions and you may try the ungraded activities as many times as you like.

How will my final grade be determined? 
Your final grade will be determined by eight weekly quizzes (no quiz in week 6, instead there is mid-term exam), ten weekly activities, one mid-term exam, and one final exam.

Quizzes = 30%  
Weekly Activities = 20% 
Mid-term Exam = 20% 
Final Exam = 30%

A+ = 97-100

A = 94-96

A- = 90-93

B+ = 87-89

B = 84-86

B- = 80-83

C+ = 77-79

C = 74-76

C- = 70-73

D+ = 67-69

D = 65-66

F = 0-64 

How do I get answers to questions I have related to the courses? 
Research shows that learning happens best in an active academic community, so we encourage you to post your question to the Discussion Forum. It’s likely that someone will respond to your question. The instructor of record and course facilitators will also review frequently asked questions and provide their insights. 

How do I get credit? 
In lieu of a  “Statement of Accomplishment”,  professional (certificate) credit for this course is available from UC San Diego Extension via a companion course offered directly by UC San Diego Extension. The companion course does have a fee, and builds upon the information presented in this course, with increased interactivity, assignments, and demonstration of mastery.  For more information about earning credit for this course, please visit: UC San Diego Extension.  

If you would like to earn credit, register for both the MOOC and companion course. If you don&#39;t wish to earn credit, then register for the MOOC only. 
Registration Links: 

Earn Credit companion course: UC San Diego Extension
MOOC - Climate Change in Four Dimensions 

TECHNICAL SUPPORT 
What are the technical requirements for being able to use this course? 
System Requirements
For the optimal online learning experience, your system must meet the following requirements:

Hardware
Software &amp; Media Players
Operating Systems
Browsers
Connections
Hardware
The following hardware is required to access course materials:

Monitor—800x600, 65000+ colors (16 bit color or greater)
Audio—speakers or headphones
Software &amp; Media Players
Install or verify the version of your media players and plug-ins.

Macromedia Flash Player (for .flv and .swf files) must be installed manually. Version 7 and above.
Adobe Reader (for .pdf files) must be installed manually. Version 5 and above.
Operating Systems
Our online courses are accessible on the following operating systems: 
Windows XP (32-bit)
Windows Vista (32-bit and 64-bit)
Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit)
Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard
Mac OS X 10.6 Snow Leopard
Browsers
Our online courses are accessible via the following browsers:

Windows Systems
Internet Explorer 8 and 9
Firefox 3.6 and newer stable versions
Chrome (stable versions)
Macintosh Systems
Safari 4 and 5
Firefox 3.6 and newer stable versions
Chrome (stable versions)

Enable the following features in your browser:

Java 6 (also called 1.6)
JavaScript
Cookies for ucsdextension.blackboard.com

Disable the following features in your browser:

Pop-Up Blocking—If your browser or firewall employs pop-up blocking technology, please disable pop-up blocking entirely or for http://coursera.com.
If you would like further instructions on how to perform these actions on your browser, go to the Browser Tuneup page.

Connections
UC San Diego Extension online courses provide a rich multimedia experience and employ large documents, including audio and graphics files. It is unlikely that a dial up connection will be fast enough to provide a satisfactory experience. We recommend users connect to our online course materials via a high-speed broadband connection (including Local Area Networks (LANs).

Something on the site isn&#39;t working. Who should I contact? 
Please send us an email with your question: unex-mooc@ucsd.edu 
Please type &quot;MOOC&quot; in the subject header.  Thank you!</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.coursera.org/course/911aftermath</field>
	<field name="course_title">9/11 and Its Aftermath -- Part I | Coursera</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">7 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">3-4hours of work / week</field>
	<field name="course_language">English</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">David Schanzer</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">David Schanzer</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Duke University</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Duke University</field>
	<field name="course_category">Social Sciences</field>
	<field name="course_intro">9/11 and Its Aftermath -- Part I
This course will explore the forces that led to the 9/11 attacks and the policies the United States adopted in response. We will examine the phenomenon of modern terrorism, the development of the al Qai&#39;da ideology, and the process by which individuals radicalize towards violence.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About the Course
The attacks of September 11, 2001, were a seminal moment in modern history. They demonstrated the ability of non-state actors to inflict serious damage on the world&#39;s greatest superpower and exposed the vulnerability of the entire global community to catastrophic acts of terrorism. 

To understand the causes of the attacks, 9/11 and Its Aftermath -- Part I will examine the phenomenon of terrorism, in general, and, more specifically, the radical ideology developed and propagated by Osama bin Laden through al Qai&#39;da. We will consider why individuals are attracted to this ideology and how they radicalize to violence. We will also explore the way in which the United States addressed terrorism prior to 9/11 and the policy challenges it (and its allies around the globe) faced in the immediate aftermath of the attacks. 

The second part of this course -- to be offered sometime in 2014 -- will examine the policy &quot;aftermath&quot; of 9/11. Part II will examine how the United States changed its policies in response to 9/11 in three areas: the use of military force, law enforcement and intelligence activities, and homeland security. We will trace the evolution of these policies from the Bush to the Obama Administration and critically assess the overall counter-terrorism strategy. 

Together, these courses will provide the background necessary to understand why 9/11 occurred, and consider the range of options that democratic nations can use to counteract this form of political violence.  
Course Syllabus
Course Topics

Week 1: The 9/11 Attacks
Week 2: What is Terrorism?
Week 3: A Primer on Islam
Week 4: The Al Qai&#39;da Ideology
Week 5: The Radicalization Process
Week 6: Counterterrorism Pre-9/11
Week 7: September 12, 2001
Recommended Background
No background is required. 
Suggested Readings
There will be weekly readings that will either be provided as PDFs or as links. You will not be required to buy any texts. 

If you are interested in learning more, I can highly recommend Lawrence Wright&#39;s The Looming Tower and The 9/11 Commission Report.
Course Format
Each week will consist of lecture videos, readings, and an assessment. Along with content lectures by Professor Schanzer, there will be videos of student discussions and interviews with various experts. There will be multiple opportunities for engagement with fellow students and Professor Schanzer through Google Hangouts and the discussion forums.

Students will submit weekly posts commenting on an aspect of the materials. In addition, there will be either a quiz or peer assessment for each topic. Students will be asked to think critically about the subject matter and form their own opinions -- this is not a course with right and wrong answers. Rather, it is designed to provide the information necessary to engage in informed debate about difficult issues, think critically, assess tradeoffs, and express your own opinions. 
FAQ
Will I get a Statement of Accomplishment after completing this class?

Yes. Students who successfully complete the class with a 70% or better will receive a Statement of Accomplishment signed by the instructor. Students who complete the class with a 85% or better will receive a Statement of Accomplishment with Distinction. The Signature Track will be available for this course.

What is the code of ethics for this course?

There is an ethics code relating to your work for the course and participation on the discussion forums. Students will be required to agree to the Coursera Honor Code, which requires that students do their own work and act honorably on assessments. Vibrant and open discussion will be encourage on the discussion forums. Education is advanced by exposure to a full range of ideas and vigorous exchange of perspectives and opinions. Nonetheless, comments that make no contribution to thoughtful discourse and appear to be intended primarily to offend, intimidate, demean, or stifle other will not be tolerated. Posts that violate this standard will be removed from the forums and students unwilling to abide by this standard will be removed from the course.

What is the most important thing I will learn about in this class?

The main objective of the course is to teach students to think critically about controversial, important issues. You will learn to form opinions and craft arguments that are based on facts and substance, not mere feelings or conjecture. You will be exposed to the wide variety of opinion around the globe about the ideas promoted by al Qai’da and like minded groups and the origins of the 9/11 attacks. The course will provide you the basis to be an informed participant in these discussions and debates. You will not be taught what to think or believe about these issues. Rather, you will be provided background information and exposure to ideas so you can to develop your own views and reach your own conclusions from an informed perspective.</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.coursera.org/course/aboriginaled</field>
	<field name="course_title">Aboriginal Worldviews and Education | Coursera</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">4 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">6-8hours of work / week</field>
	<field name="course_language">English</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Jean-Paul Restoule</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Jean-Paul Restoule</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of Toronto</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">University of Toronto</field>
	<field name="course_category">Humanities</field>
	<field name="course_category">Education</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Aboriginal Worldviews and Education
This course will explore indigenous ways of knowing and how this knowledge can inform education to the benefit of all students.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About the Course
Intended for both Aboriginal and non-Aboriginal learners, this course will explore indigenous ways of knowing and how they can benefit all students. Topics include historical, social, and political issues in Aboriginal education; terminology; cultural, spiritual and philosophical themes in Aboriginal worldviews; and how Aboriginal worldviews can inform professional programs and practices, including but not limited to the field of education. 
Recommended Background
This course is appropriate for anyone with an interest in learning (or learning more) about Aboriginal history and world views. No prior knowledge is required.
Suggested Readings
Each week, students will be introduced to relevant readings and resources (most publicly available on the Internet).
Course Format
Each week will focus on a topic, with several short  videos (5 to 20 minutes each) featuring Jean-Paul Restoule and, for some topics, guests, as well as one or two readings. Each video will include 1 or 2 integrated quiz questions. There will also be a short writing assignment or quiz each week, as well as opportunities for on-line discussions.
FAQ
Will I get a certificate after completing this class?
Students who successfully complete the class will receive a statement of accomplishment signed by the instructor.</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.coursera.org/course/ac</field>
	<field name="course_title">Analytic Combinatorics | Coursera</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">6 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">6-8hours of work / week</field>
	<field name="course_language">English</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Robert Sedgewick</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Robert Sedgewick</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Robert Sedgewick</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Princeton University</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Princeton University</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Princeton University</field>
	<field name="course_category">Computer Science: Theory</field>
	<field name="course_category">Mathematics</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Analytic Combinatorics
Analytic Combinatorics teaches a calculus that enables precise quantitative predictions of large combinatorial structures. This course introduces the symbolic method to derive functional relations among ordinary, exponential, and multivariate generating functions, and methods in complex analysis for deriving accurate asymptotics from the GF equations.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About the Course
Analytic Combinatorics is based on formal methods for deriving functional relationships on generating functions and asymptotic analysis treating those functions as functions in the complex plane. This course covers the symbolic method for defining generating functions immediately from combinatorial constructions, then develops methods for directly deriving asymptotic results from those generating functions, using complex asymptotics, singularity analysis, saddle-point asymptotics, and limit laws. The course teaches the precept &quot;if you can specify it, you can analyze it&quot;.
Course Syllabus
Lecture  1  Combinatorial Structures and OGFs
Lecture  2  Labelled Structures and EGFs
Lecture  3  Combinatorial Parameters and MGFs
Lecture  4  Complex Analysis, Rational and Meromorphic Asymptotics
Lecture  5  Applications of Rational and Meromorphic Asymptotics
Lecture  6  Singularity Analysis of Generating Functions
Lecture  7  Applications of Singularity Analysis
Lecture  8  Saddle-Point Asymptotics
Recommended Background
Familiarity with recurrences, generating functions, asymptotics and basic combinatorics as taught in Analysis of Algorithms. Basic familiarity with programming in Java and the algorithms and data structures covered in Algorithms, Part I is helpful but not required. The video From Analysis of Algorithms to Analytic Combinatorics: A Journey with Philippe Flajolet, is an optional overview that tries to answer the question &quot;What is Analytic Combinatorics&quot; and to give some historical perspective.
Suggested Readings
This course is based on the textbook Analytic Combinatorics by Flajolet and Sedgewick. The (free) web materials associated with the course and the textbook can be found at http://ac.cs.princeton.edu/home/
Course Format
There will be one lecture (about 80 minutes) and a problem set each week.
FAQ
Does Princeton award credentials or reports regarding my work in this course?
No certificates, statements of accomplishment, or other credentials will be awarded in connection with this course.</field>
</doc>
</add>