<add>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.edx.org/course/anux/anux-anu-astro2x-exoplanets-1443</field>
	<field name="course_title">ANUx: ANU-ASTRO2x: Exoplanets | edX</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">10 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">3 hours/week</field>
	<field name="course_language">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Brian Schmidt</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Paul Francis</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Brian Schmidt led the team that discovered dark energy – work which won him the 2011 Nobel Prize for Physics. He is a Laureate Fellow and Distinguished Professor at the Australian National University. Raised in Montana and Alaska, USA, he obtained a PhD from Harvard before coming to Australia, where his passions include astrophysics and his vineyard in the hills near Canberra. Brian has won almost every possible award and distinction for his work - work that has revolutionised our understanding of the origin and fate of our universe. He is continuing his work using exploding stars to study the Universe, and is leading Australian National University&#39;s effort to build the SkyMapper telescope, a new facility that will provide a comprehensive digital map of the southern sky from ultraviolet through near infrared wavelengths.</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Paul Francis is a prize-winning educator, science communicator and astrophysics researcher. He obtained a PhD from the University of Cambridge, has worked with NASA, and is well known for his work on the spectra of quasars. Famous for his unorthodox teaching style, his strange taste in waistcoats and for his discovery that some black holes are actually pink, he divides his time between astrophysics research and teaching. His research interests include comets, giant space blobs and hidden quasars. He has won many awards for both teaching and science communication. He is currently trying to work out why the tails of distant comets don’t point the direction they should.</field>
	<field name="course_category">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Exploring the mysteries of exoplanets - planets around other stars.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About this Course

The discovery of exoplanets is one of the greatest revolutions in modern astrophysics. Twenty years ago, we had no idea whether any of the countless stars out there beyond our solar system had planets or not. Today, things are totally different. Over one thousand planetary systems have been discovered. The universe is teeming with planets. And what strange planets they are - hot Jupiter-like planets skimming the surfaces of their stars, cold and lonely free-floating planets far from any star, planets made of diamond, planets with rain made of glass, super-Earths and even planets orbiting neutron stars. In this course we’ll bring you up-to-date with the latest research on exoplanets, and how it has revolutionised our understanding of the formation of solar systems like our own. This course is designed for people who would like to get a deeper understanding of these mysteries than that offered by popular science articles and shows. You will need reasonable high-school level Maths and Physics to get the most out of this course. This is the second of four ANUx courses which together make up The Australian National University&#39;s first year astrophysics program. It follows on from the introductory course on the Greatest Unsolved Mysteries of the Universe. It is not necessary to have done the introductory course first: all necessary background material is repeated here. It will be followed by courses on the violent universe and on cosmology.Prerequisites

High school maths and physics.</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.edx.org/course/anux/anux-anu-india1x-engaging-india-1376</field>
	<field name="course_title">ANUx: ANU-INDIA1x: Engaging India | edX</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">10 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">3-5 hours per week</field>
	<field name="course_language">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Dr. McComas Taylor</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Dr. Peter Friedlander</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">The sight of a peacock in a field of marigolds, the sound of temple drums and gongs at dawn and the dazzling smile of a young fellow proudly operating his own tea stall: these are the sorts of experiences that have kept McComas Taylor going back to India time and again over the past decade and more. His background is in Sanskrit literature, the classical language of India, and his current research focuses on the role of Sanskrit in contemporary Hindu practice. McComas also teaches award-winning courses on the great Indian epics, the Mahābhārata and the Rāmāyaṇa, as well as on ancient and modern Indian history. He also has degrees in Chinese language, and broader interests in Tibet and Mongolia.

मक्कोमस टेलर


गेंदे के फूलों के खेत में मोर के नाच का दृश्य। भोर में मंदिरों की घंटियों का नाद और एक चाय की दुकान के मालिक की भीनी-सी मुस्कान। यही वे सब बाते हैं जो मक्कोमस टेलर को पिछले एक दशक से ज़्यादा के समय से बार-बार भारत की ओर खींच रही हैं। वे भारत की पारंपरिक साहित्यिक भाषा, संस्कृत, के विद्वान हैं और वे इस समय शोध कर रहे हैं कि आधुनिक हिंदू परंपराओं में संस्कृत क्या भूमिका निभाती है। मक्कोमस भारत के महाकाव्यों, महाभारत और रामायण, तथा प्राचीन एवं आधुनिक भारत के इतिहास पर पुरस्कार सम्मानित पाठ्यक्रम भी पढ़ाते हैं। उन्होंने चीनी भाषा में कई उपाधियाँ भी हासिल की हैं और तिब्बत और मंगोलिया के बारे में रूचि रखते हैं।</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Dr Peter Friedlander left London in 1977 with the intent to travel to Australia. On the way he visited India, and was so fascinated by its cultures and peoples that he didn’t manage to get to Australia until 1989. Peter has been teaching and researching about India ever since. He has taught Hindi and Indian cultural studies in India, Singapore and Australia. In 2012 Peter was the recipient of the World Hindi Conference Award for his contributions to the teaching of Hindi Language and Literature. His research publications cover subjects such as Hindi language, literature and teaching pedagogy, South Asian religious traditions, and the role of Buddhism in India and the world.

पीटर फ़्रीडलैंडर


सन् 1977 में डा. पीटर फ़्रीडलैंडर ऑस्ट्रेलिया आने के लिये लंदन से रवाना हुये। रास्ते में वे भारत में रुके और भारत की संस्कृति और उसके लोगों से इतने प्रभावित हुये कि ये वहीं रह गये और सन् 1989 तक ऑस्ट्रेलिया नहीं आये। तब से अब तक पीटर भारत पर शोध कर रहे हैं और विश्वविद्यालयों में पढ़ाते हैं। उन्होंने भारत, सिंगापुर और ऑस्ट्रेलिया में हिन्दी और भारतीय संस्कृति के विषयों पर शिक्षा दी है। सन् 2012 में हिन्दी भाषा और साहित्य की शिक्षा में रहे उनके योगदान के लिये उन्हें विश्व हिन्दी सम्मेलन पुरस्कार से सम्मानित किया गया था। उनके शोध प्रकाशनों में कई प्रकार के विषय शामिल हैं, जैसे, हिन्दी भाषा, साहित्य और शिक्षण, दक्षिण एशिया की धार्मिक परम्पराएँ तथा भारत और विश्व में बौध धर्म की भूमिका।</field>
	<field name="course_category">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_intro">A course that examines some of the factors that have shaped India and what makes India the country it is today. |  इस पाठ्यक्रम में हम कुछ चुने हुए तत्वों का विश्लेषण करेंगे जिनसे भारत का विकास प्रभावित हुआ है। इसके साथ हम आधुनिक भारत के वास्तविक रूप के बारे में विचार-विमर्श करेंगे।</field>
	<field name="course_body">About this Course

This course is presented in both English and Hindi. Videos will feature Hindi subtitles.

This course offers an overview of contemporary India and explores its role as one of the dominant economic and military powers of Asia. We begin with a discussion on India as a multilingual society.  The entire course will be available in both English and Hindi.

The central focus of the course is an examination of contemporary issues in India. This includes perspectives on how Indian culture and language are being affected by the boom in technology: sections on politics and nationalism; economics and the implications of recent moves toward liberalisation of the economy; and security, international relations, and regionalism. In addition, we will examine India’s role in South Asian politics and current issues relating to its regional neighbours in Asia. The aim of the course is to provide students with a comprehensive and wide-ranging overview of India in order that they may better understand its role in the world.

यह पाठ्यक्रम हमें आधुनिक भारत के बारे में एक संक्षिप्त विवरण देता है। और उसके साथ यह भी दर्शाता है कि किस तरह से भारत आज एशिया का एक प्रभावशाली आर्थिक और सैन्य सत्ता बन गया है। इस पाठ्यक्रम की शुरुआत हम भारत के बहुभाषी समाज पर चर्चा से करेंगे।   

यह पाठ्यक्रम हिन्दी और अंग्रेज़ी दोनों भाषाओं में उपलब्ध होगा।

इस पाठ्यक्रम का केंद्र बिन्दू भारत के समकालीन मुद्दों का विश्लेषण करना है। इस में भिन्न-भिन्न दृष्टिकोणों से विचार प्रस्तुत किये जायेंगे कि भारतीय संस्कृतियाँ और भाषाएँ किस तरह से टेक्नोलोजी में आई तेज़ी से प्रभावित हुईं हैं। इसके अलावा हम इन विषयों के बारे में बातचीत करेंगे: राजनीति और राष्ट्रवाद, अर्थशास्त्र और अर्थव्यवस्था के उदारीकरण से हुये परिवर्तन का असर, सुरक्षा, भारत की विदेश नीति और क्षेत्रवाद। इन सब के साथ हम यह भी देखेंगे कि दक्षिण एशिया की राजनीति में भारत ने क्या भूमिका निभाई है और उसके पड़ोसी देशों के संबंध में विचार करेंगे। इस पाठ्यक्रम का उद्देश्य है विद्यार्थियों को भारत के बारे में विस्तृत जानकारी देना ताकि वे ज़्यादा अच्छी तरह से भारत और विश्व में भारत की भूमिका को समझ सकें।Prerequisites

None</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.edx.org/course/australian-national-university/australian-national-university-anu-1347</field>
	<field name="course_title">ANUx: ANU-ASTRO1x: Greatest Unsolved Mysteries of the Universe | edX</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">10 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">3 hours per week</field>
	<field name="course_language">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Brian Schmidt</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Paul Francis</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Brian Schmidt led the team that discovered dark energy – work which won him the 2011 Nobel Prize for Physics. He is a Laureate Fellow and Distinguished Professor at the Australian National University. Raised in Montana and Alaska, USA, he obtained a PhD from Harvard before coming to Australia, where his passions include astrophysics and his vineyard in the hills near Canberra. Brian has won almost every possible award and distinction for his work - work that has revolutionised our understanding of the origin and fate of our universe. He is continuing his work using exploding stars to study the Universe, and is leading Australian National University&#39;s effort to build the SkyMapper telescope, a new facility that will provide a comprehensive digital map of the southern sky from ultraviolet through near infrared wavelengths.</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Paul Francis is a prize-winning educator, science communicator and astrophysics researcher. He obtained a PhD from the University of Cambridge, has worked with NASA, and is well known for his work on the spectra of quasars. Famous for his unorthodox teaching style, his strange taste in waistcoats and for his discovery that some black holes are actually pink, he divides his time between astrophysics research and teaching. His research interests include comets, giant space blobs and hidden quasars. He has won many awards for both teaching and science communication. He is currently trying to work out why the tails of distant comets don’t point the direction they should.</field>
	<field name="course_category">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Exploring the biggest mysteries of modern astrophysics.</field>
	<field name="course_body">About this Course

Despite spectacular recent progress, there is still a lot we don&#39;t know about our universe. We don&#39;t know why the Big Bang happened. We don&#39;t know what most of the universe is made of. We don&#39;t know whether there is life in space. We don&#39;t know how planets form, how black holes get so big, or where the first stars have gone. This course will take you through nine of the greatest unsolved problems of modern astrophysics. We can&#39;t promise you the answers, but we will explain what we do and don&#39;t know, and give you an up-to-date understanding of current research. This course is designed for people who would like to get a deeper understanding of these mysteries than that offered by popular science articles and shows. You will need reasonable high-school level Maths and Physics to get the most out of this course. This is the first of four ANUx courses which together make up the Australian National University&#39;s first year astrophysics program. It will be followed by courses on exoplanets, on the violent universe, and on cosmology.Prerequisites

High school math and physics.</field>
</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.edx.org/course/berkleex/berkleex-bcm-mb110x-introduction-music-1184</field>
	<field name="course_title">404: You&#39;ve reached this page by accident | edX</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_workload">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_language">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_category">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_body">Undefined</field>
	</doc>
<doc>
	<field name="course_url">https://www.edx.org/course/caltechx/caltechx-cs1156x-learning-data-1120</field>
	<field name="course_title">CaltechX: CS1156x: Learning From Data | edX</field>
	<field name="course_price">Free</field>
	<field name="course_length">10 weeks</field>
	<field name="course_workload">10 hours per week.</field>
	<field name="course_language">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_instructor">Yaser S. Abu-Mostafa</field>
	<field name="course_instructor_intro">Dr. Abu-Mostafa is a Professor of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science at the California Institute of Technology. His main fields of expertise are machine learning and computational finance. He is the co-author of Amazon&#39;s machine learning bestseller Learning From Data.

Dr. Abu-Mostafa received the Clauser Prize for the most original doctoral thesis at Caltech. He won various Caltech and national teaching awards, including the Feynman Prize in 1996. He is the co-founder of the Neural Information Processing Systems (NIPS) annual conference, the top international conference on machine learning. He chaired a number of conferences on applying machine learning to finance, including Computational Finance (CF-99). In 2005, the Hertz Foundation established a perpetual graduate fellowship named the Abu-Mostafa Fellowship in his honor.

Dr. Abu-Mostafa currently serves on a number of scientific advisory boards, and has served as a technical consultant on machine learning for several companies, including Citibank for 9 years. He has numerous technical publications including 3 articles in Scientific American, as well as several keynote lectures at international conferences.</field>
	<field name="course_category">Undefined</field>
	<field name="course_intro">Introductory Machine Learning course covering theory, algorithms and applications. Our focus is on real understanding, not just &quot;knowing.&quot;</field>
	<field name="course_body">About this Course

*Note - This is an Archived course*

This is a past/archived course. At this time, you can only explore this course in a self-paced fashion. Certain features of this course may not be active, but many people enjoy watching the videos and working with the materials. Make sure to check for reruns of this course.

This is an introductory course in machine learning (ML) that covers the basic theory, algorithms, and applications. ML is a key technology in Big Data, and in many financial, medical, commercial, and scientific applications. It enables computational systems to automatically learn how to perform a desired task based on information extracted from the data. ML has become one of the hottest fields of study today, taken up by undergraduate and graduate students from 15 different majors at Caltech. This course balances theory and practice, and covers the mathematical as well as the heuristic aspects. The lectures follow each other in a story-like fashion:

What is learning?
Can a machine learn?
How to do it?
How to do it well?
Take-home lessons.
The topics in the story line are covered by 18 lectures of about 60 minutes each plus Q&amp;A.

Lecture 1: The Learning Problem
Lecture 2: Is Learning Feasible?
Lecture 3: The Linear Model I
Lecture 4: Error and Noise
Lecture 5: Training versus Testing
Lecture 6: Theory of Generalization
Lecture 7: The VC Dimension
Lecture 8: Bias-Variance Tradeoff
Lecture 9: The Linear Model II
Lecture 10: Neural Networks
Lecture 11: Overfitting
Lecture 12: Regularization
Lecture 13: Validation
Lecture 14: Support Vector Machines
Lecture 15: Kernel Methods
Lecture 16: Radial Basis Functions
Lecture 17: Three Learning Principles
Lecture 18: EpiloguePrerequisites

Basic probability, matrices, and calculus. Familiarity with some programming language or platform will help with the homework.

FAQs

Do I need to buy a textbook?
No. The videos and slides that are provided here are sufficient.

Is this a real Caltech course?
Is this course hard?</field>
</doc>
</add>